{
    "subject": "resource/Adobe_Persuasion",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Presentation_program",
    "human_readable": "Adobe Persuasion is a Presentation program.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9633228778839111,
            "question": "Is Adobe Persuasion a popular presentation software?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9438027739524841,
            "question": "What is the purpose of a presentation program like Adobe Persuasion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219180345535278,
            "question": "Can you create presentations with Adobe Persuasion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921465277671814,
            "question": "What type of program is Adobe Persuasion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8367024660110474,
            "question": "How does Adobe Persuasion compare to other presentation programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7734699249267578,
            "question": "What is Adobe Persuasion used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756884753704071,
            "question": "What are some features of Adobe Persuasion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7562767267227173,
            "question": "Is Adobe Persuasion a design tool?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5148317813873291,
            "question": "Who would benefit from using Adobe Persuasion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49781009554862976,
            "question": "Are there any alternatives to Adobe Persuasion?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adobe Persuasion is a Presentation program.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3177_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who would benefit from using Adobe Persuasion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3177_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Adobe Persuasion a design tool?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3177_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some features of Adobe Persuasion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3177_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3177_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Adobe Persuasion is a presentation program, both in the form of direct statements and through details about its features and usage. Therefore, the information supports the statement \"Adobe Persuasion is a Presentation program.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}